[{"id": 2808, "question": "A lot more people are about to get a chance to buy Google Glass. It's the Internet-connected eyewear that has become the hottest sale. Google will sell the \"Explorer\" version of Glass to any U.S. person who places an online order for the device beginning at 9am. PDT April 15. The product will cost $1,500. Google is saying how many sets of Glass will be available during the limited-time offer. This version of Glass, though, still isn't the perfect product that Google hopes to sell in stores later this year. For now, Google is still trying to recruit more people willing to serve as volunteers for its attempt to build a wearable device that features some of the same feature as a smart phone. \" Our Explorers are moms, bakers, surgeons, rockers, and each new Explorer has brought a new view that...\n\nQ: What is special about Google Glass?", "options": ["People can only order it online.", "It's cheaper than the ordinary glasses.", "People can explore the Internet with it.", "It doesn't contain any actual glass in the future."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1062, "question": "In recent years many countries of the world have been faced with the problem of how to make their workers more productive. Some experts claim the answer is to make jobs more varied. But do more various jobs lead to greater productivity? There is evidence to suggest that while variety certainly makes the worker's life more enjoyable, it does not actually make him work harder. As far as increasing productivity is concerned, then variety is not an important factor. Other experts feel that giving the worker freedom to do his job in his own way is important, and there is no doubt that this is true. The problem is that this kind of freedom cannot easily be given in the modern factory with its complicated machinery which must be used in a fixed way. Thus while freedom of choice may be important, ...\n\nQ: In the article, the word \"productivity\" means   _  .", "options": ["the activity of producing something", "the production volume in a time unit", "the plan and the method of production", "both the quantity and quality of a product"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1584, "question": "Zoe, Damacela, 19, didn't have nice clothes when she was young. It wasn't easy for Zoe's hard-working single mother to make ends meet. They moved in and out of homeless shelters. Everything changed for Zoe in grade nine. At that time, she heard about a sewing class at her school. She signed up and couldn't wait to turn her designs into clothes. The color of the first dress she made was white-black strips. Soon the clothes she wore were all made by her. Other girls at school loved her designs too. They asked her if they could buy dresses from her. Zoe sold her first dress for $13. Unfortunately, it cost her $25 to make the dress. \"I had the creativity in designs,\" says Zoe. \"But I really had no idea about business.\" Zoe kept selling the clothes she designed. Her business was booming, and ev...\n\nQ: Zoe advised the teens    _    .", "options": ["to make efforts to achieve their dreams", "to design and make their own clothes", "to try every means to become famous", "to do whatever they would like to"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2986, "question": "Though the facts that too many people on earth and a too rapid increase in the number added each year are not in argument, we always begin the discussion of \"population as global issue\" with what most persons mean like this. It was quite right to compare demographic growth to \"a long, thin powder fuse that bums steadily and hesitatingly until it finally reaches the charge and explodes\". To understand the current situation, which is characterized by rapid increases in population, it is necessary to understand the history of population trends. Rapid growth is a comparatively recent phenomenon. Looking back at the 8,000 years of demographic history, we find that populations have been virtually stable or growing very slightly for most of human history. For most of our ancestors, life was hard,...\n\nQ: The author of the passage intends to  _  .", "options": ["warn people against the population explosion in the near future", "find out the cause of rapid increase in population in recent years", "present us a brief and clear picture of the demographic growth", "compare the demographic growth pattern in the past with that after 1650"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3440, "question": "Nickname: Hawaii's Island of Adventure Size: 4,028 square miles Population: 148,677. The most heavily populated areas are Hilo on the east side and Kailua-Kona on the west. Temperature: Averages between 71degFand 77degF year around ( _ ). Beaches: 47 Golf Courts: 20 Highest Peak: Mauna Kea, 13,796 feet. Agriculture: The bulk of Hawaii's farming products are grown and processed on the Big Island, including coffee, macadamia nuts and papaya. Lodging: 9,655 rooms total; nightly rates range from $35-$5,000. Airports: Hilo International Airport on the east side and Kona International Airport on the west side. Rental Cars: All of the nationally known rental car companies have locations at Hilo International and Kona International Airports as well as many resorts. In addition, Hilo, Kona and the ...\n\nQ: _   are mostly interested in reading the passage.", "options": ["Students", "Tourists", "Businessmen", "Officials"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2089, "question": "The percentage of districts that require elementary schools to teach physical education increased, to 93% last year from 83% in 2000. But just 4% of elementary schools, 8% of middle schools and 2% of high schools provided physical education each school day, as is recommended by the disease control agency. One-fifth of schools did not require physical education at all. In 2004, Congress passed a law requiring each school district to develop a \"wellness policy\" to promote the students' health by setting goals for nutrition education and physical activity. Those policies are just now taking effect, and some school administrators predict that the next survey will show more marked improvements. Some schools have set out to place health education on the same requirement with academics. In Los An...\n\nQ: What is the best title for this passage?", "options": ["How to change children's eating habits", "Improve students' physical health by developing their nutrition education", "Only a little percentage of students are taught physical education", "Healthy habits should be taught in schools"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1495, "question": "Love Is Just a Thread Sometimes I really doubt whether there is love between my parents.Every day they are very busy trying to earn money to pay the high tuition for us.They don't act in the romantic ways that I read in books or I see on TV.\" I love you\" is too luxurious for them to say .Sending flowers to each other on Valentine's Day is even more _ .My father is easy to lose his temper, especially when he's very tired from the hard work. One day, my mother was sewing a quilt.I silently sat beside her and asked her if there was love between them.\" What?\" she replied, still doing her work.My mother stopped her work and raised her head with surprise.She didn't answer immediately.Then she bowed her head and continued sewing the quilt.I was in a great embarrassment and I didn't know what to d...\n\nQ: Why does the author sometimes doubt that there is real love between her parents?", "options": ["Because they are very busy earning money for the high tuition.", "Because they don't act in the romantic ways.", "Because her father is easy to lose his temper to her mother", "Because \" I love you\" is too luxurious for them to say"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 232, "question": "Nothing is more frustrating than not being able to sleep, tossing and turning . Your mind is racing, going over everything that happened that day. Night noises keep you awake. What can you do? Here are some things you can do to help you to fall asleep. Sleep only when sleepy This reduces the time you are awake in bed. If you can't fall asleep within 20 minutes, get up and do something boring until you feel sleepy. Don't expose yourself to bright light while you are up. The light tells your brain that it is time to wake up. Don't take naps This will ensure that you are tired at bedtime. If you just can't make it through the day without a nap, sleep less than one hour, and take a nap before 3 p.m. Get up and go to bed at the same time every day Even on weekends! When your sleep cycle has a r...\n\nQ: According to the passage, one had better not take naps   _  .", "options": ["when they have many things to do", "before 3 p.m", "for over one hour", "when they are tired"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1680, "question": "The round-the-clock availability that cell phones have brought to people's lives may be _ amily life, a new study suggests. The study, which followed more than 1300 adults over 2 years, found that those who consistently used a mobile phone through out the study period were more likely to report negative \"spillover\" between work and home life--and, in turn, less satisfaction with their family life. Spillover(,) actually means that the line between work and home began to become unclear. Work life may invade home life--when a parent is taking job-related calls at home, for instance--or family issues may start to take up work time. For example, a child may call Mom at work, telling her \"the microwave exploded\", explained Noelle Chesley, an assistant professor of society at the University of Wi...\n\nQ: What is the author's attitude towards round-the-clock availability of the cell phone?", "options": ["Curious", "Positive", "Subjective", "Objective"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2472, "question": "My mother used to ask me what the most important part of the body is. Through the years Iwould take a guess at what I thought was the correct answer. When I was younger, I thought sound was very important to us as humans, so I said: \"My ears, Mommy.\" She said: \"No. Many people are deaf. But you keep thinking about it and I will ask you again soon.\"Several years passed before she asked me again. Since making my first attempt, I had contemplated the correct answer. So this time I told her: \"Mommy, sight is very important to everybody, so it must be our eyes.\" She looked at me and told me: \"You are learning fast, but the answer is not correct because there are many people who are blind.\" Mother asked me a couple more times and always her answer was \"No. But you are getting smarter every year,...\n\nQ: The mother ask the question again after the grandfather died because   _  .", "options": ["the answer was a way of honoring the grandfather.", "at that moment, other body parts were less important.", "the answer needed to be given to all members of the family.", "at that moment the answer seemed especially true."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1078, "question": "What did you dream about last night? Did your teeth fall out or did you fly? Maybe you died or someone you know did.Or maybe you were back in high school.These are among the most common dreams people have and they all mean something.Here are some of the most common dreams and their interpretations or symbolism. Dreams of flying.Dreams of flying represent feelings of freedom that may result from an instance when you overcome a limitation or obstacle.Usually, children have more flying dreams than adults, because children are more open to their possibilities, and adults have often accepted limitations imposed by society. Teeth falling out.Food in a dream is symbolic of knowledge because food nourishes the physical body and knowledge nourishes the soul.Teeth are a means to break down food or k...\n\nQ: If you dream of being unprepared for a \"high school test, it means  _  .", "options": ["you' re trying to learn something", "you will certainly fail in the test", "you will be scolded by your teacher", "you' re not well prepared for the test"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2208, "question": "Christmas Day, the birthday of Jesus Christ, is the most important festival in prefix = st1 /Britainand some other countries. On Christmas Eve, people usually tell their children to put their stockings at the end of their beds before they go to sleep. Children believe Santa Claus, with the other name of Father Christmas, will come during the night and fill their stockings with Christmas presents. Actually , Father Christmas is children's father. He dresses up in a red coat and waits until children fall asleep. Then he goes into children's bedrooms, and puts small presents in their stockings. When children are no longer young, they know who Father Christmas really is. Not only children but also their parents enjoy Christmas stockings. They also have stockings. Early on the morning of Christ...\n\nQ: Christmas Day is  _  .", "options": ["the birthday of Jesus Christ", "the only day for giving presents", "the only day for receiving presents", "the day for playing games"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2350, "question": "Centerville High School Essay Contest \"Write All About It\" Calling All Aspiring Authors--Centerville High School Essay Contest *Rules 1.Students are asked to present essays of 500 to 700 words of their own work. Any essay containing material plagiarized from another source will be disqualified . 2.Manuscripts should be typed double-spaced,with the student's name,address,and grade level on a separate sheet of paper. 3.Essays must be turned in by 4:00 p.m. on November 30.They can be brought to Mrs. Elton in Rom 104 or to Mr. Markham in the school library. *Essay-Writing Tips 1.Catch your readers' interests--Your opening should immediately pull your readers into your essay. Asking a question or starting with an story,quotation,or surprising statement is a good way to do this. 2.Create a pictu...\n\nQ: Information in the passage suggests that  _  .", "options": ["the essay contest has been carefully planned", "the students of the school are all athletic lovers", "most essay contestants have published their work previously", "Mr. Markham is an English teacher at Centerville High School"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2313, "question": "Unemployment in Europe has recently hit record highs. Although Denmark has been protected from economic problems thanks to its low public debt, qualified professionals are still finding it tough to get a job. Danish marketing firm Reputation Copenhagen has come up with a way of helping academics get noticed -- putting them on display in storefront windows. Many highly-trained professionals, ranging from former CEOs to lawyers and tax experts, are currently finding it increasingly difficult to find proper employment on the Danish job market. Some of them have been trying for years, leaving their resumes with dozens of companies, without ever hearing back from them, and are now at a point where they are willing to try anything, even putting themselves in display windows like goods, hoping to...\n\nQ: Which of the following words can be used to describe Peitersen?", "options": ["Independent.", "Creative.", "Sensitive.", "Cautious."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3312, "question": "There has been much discussion recently about reducing the weight of English in China's high-stake tests such as the national college entrance examination. It is argued by some applauding the recent change to reduce the importance of English in tests so that it will lead students to focus more on learning Chinese. The TV program Writing in Chinese has exposed the problem that students and the general public cannot write in Chinese as they used to do. Some blame the design of the curriculum for giving English an equal or greater amount of emphasis, which might have contributed to the failure in teaching Chinese. But this is probably not a fair accusation since children in English speaking countries cannot spell either. I doubt that studying English in itself hurts the study of Chinese. In f...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is right?", "options": ["The TV program Writing in Chinese is very popular at present.", "Good results of learning English are not worth so much time.", "Some are in favor of attaching less importance to English in exams.", "Sacrificing English can improve Chinese language education."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3350, "question": "In cities with rent control, the city government sets the maximum rent that a landlord can charge for an apartment. Supporters of rent control argue that it protects people who are living in apartments. Their rent cannot increase; therefore, they are not in danger of losing their homes. However, the critics say that after a long time, rent control may have negative effects. Landlords know that they cannot increase their profits . Therefore, they invest in other businesses where they can increase their profits. They do not invest in new buildings which would also be rent - controlled. As a result, new apartments are not built. Many people who need apartments cannot find any. According to the critics, the end result of rent control is a shortage of apartments in the city. Some theorists argu...\n\nQ: The passage tells us_.", "options": ["the relationship between supply and demand", "the possible results of government controls", "the necessity of government control", "the urgency of getting rid of government controls"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 558, "question": "EDGEWOOD-Every morning at Dixie Heights High School, customers pour into a special experiment: the district's first coffee shop run mostly by students with special learning needs. Well before classes start, students and teachers order Lattes, Cappuccinos and Hot Chocolates. Then, during the first period, teachers call in orders on their room phones, and students make deliveries. By closing time at 9.20 a.m., the shop usually sells 90 drinks. \"Whoever made the chi tea, Ms. Schatzman says it was good,\" Christy McKinley, a second year student, announced recently, after hanging up with the teacher. The shop is called the Dixie PIT, which stands for Power in Transition. Although some of the students are not disabled, many are, and the PIT helps them prepare for life after high school. They lear...\n\nQ: We know from the text that Ginger Gray   _  .", "options": ["manages the Dixie P1T program in Kenton County", "sees that the drinks meet health standards", "teaches at Dixie Heights High School", "owns the school's coffee shop"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 846, "question": "If you are looking for the place that has everything, there is only one place to visit, and that's New York. It's a whole world in a city. The World of Theater: All of New York is a stage. And it begins with Broadway. Where else can you find so many hit shows in one place? Only in New York! The World of Music: Spend an evening with Beethoven at Lincoln Center. Swing to the great jazz of Greenwich Village. Or rock yourself silly at the hottest dance spots found anywhere. The World of Art: From Rembrandt to Picasso. From Egyptian tombs to Indian teepees. Whatever kind of art you like, you will find it in New York. The World of Fine Dining: Whether it's roast Beijing duck in Chinatown, lasagna in little Italy, or the finest French coq au vin found everywhere, there is world of great taste wai...\n\nQ: This passage may be taken from  _  .", "options": ["a handbook for English learners", "a guidebook for foreign travellers", "a pocketbook for businessmen", "a storybook for local readers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1560, "question": "\"Thanks for coming,\" Everett said, shaking hands with Mr. Hanson, the town councilor . \"I'm curious about the ideas in your letter.\" Mr. Hanson nodded toward the parking lot near where they stood. \"Please tell me more.\" Everett took a deep breath. \"Ever since the school closed two years ago, this area has become worse. But if we clean up the litter and repair the fence, it will be a great place for a skateboard park.\" Mr. Hanson scanned the broken concrete, nodding. \"The old school is being adapted to a community arts centre. This area could become a vital part of the neighbourhood again.\" \"Here's a picture of a skateboard park in another town. Look how busy it is.\" Everett was relieved that the community representative seemed receptive to the idea. Mr. Hanson studied the photograph, and t...\n\nQ: How did Mr. Hanson finally feel about Everett's suggestion?", "options": ["Curious.", "Hopeful.", "Receptive.", "Enthusiastic."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2894, "question": "From Chengdu to Jiuzhaigou, you can travel along the East Line not only the other line going past Dujiangyan and Wenchuan. Take a regular bus from Chengdu Chengbei Bus Station from 9:00 to 16:30. It only takes about three hours to Jiangyou. The ticket is CNY50.00 net per person. Up along Fujiang River, you will pass the second largest city in Sichuan, Mianyang and enjoy the picturesque scenery. There is bus available to the destination from 6:30 to 13:30 in Mianyang Pingzheng Bus Station,The one way ticket is about CNY95.00 net per person. In this case, you can not get stop at Jiangyou and Pingwu. This is one option for you. In Jiangyou, visit the Former Residence of Li Bai, the famous poet in Tang Dynasty. If time permits, you can also take a look at the Doutuan Mountain, which is famous ...\n\nQ: From this passage, which of the following statement is TRUE?", "options": ["Pingwu Hotel is the only choice for foreign guests in Pingwu.", "We'd better pay the entrance fee twice in Jiuzhaigou.", "We can travel from Chengdu to Jiuzhaigou along different routes.", "Doutuan Mountain is famous for the Former Residence of Li Bai."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1745, "question": "\"Colour\" and \"color1\" , \"favourite\" and \"favorite\"\"- Have you ever wondered why Americans spell those words without a \"u\"? Is it because they are lazy? Of course not.In fact, the difference in spelling was created by Noah Webster(1758--1843) .He is a teacher who reformed English to make American identity stronger.Linguists celebrated his 250th birthday on October 16,2008.After the Revolutionary War(1775--1783) , Webster believed that Americans should have their own dictionary, rather than rely on British versions.He dropped the British \"u\" in some words.And he changed \"centre\" into \"center\" for children to learn English by spelling words more like they sounded. Webster wasn't shy about expressing his opinions.In defining preposterous (unreasonable) , he wrote: \"A Republican government in t...\n\nQ: Which of the following words can best describe Noah Webster' s work?", "options": ["Interesting", "Boring", "Unfinished", "Meaningful"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1724, "question": "Money might not grow on trees, but scientists have confirmed that gold is found in the leaves of some plants. Researchers from Australia say that the presence of the particles in an eucalyptus tree's leaves indicates that deposits are buried many meters below. They believe that the discovery offers a new way to locate the valuable metal in difficult-to-reach locations. Dr. Mel Lintern from Australia's Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization (CSIRO) said, \"We've found a lot of the easy deposits in Australia in this way. Now we are trying to find the more difficult ones that are buried tens of meters below. And the trees are providing us with a method to be able to do this.\" Using the Australian synchrotron - a vast machine that uses X-rays to explore matter in remarkabl...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true about the plant-analyzing method?", "options": ["Expensive.", "Low cost.", "Easy and simple", "environmental."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3228, "question": "Global warming is causing more than 300,000 deaths and about $125 billion in economic losses each year, according to a report by the Global Humanitarian Forum, an organization led by Annan, the former United Nations secretary general. The report, to be released Friday, analyzed data and existing studies of health, disaster, population and economic trends. It found that human-influenced climate change was raising the global death rates from illnesses including malnutrition and heat-related health problems. But even before its release, the report drew criticism from some experts on climate and risk, who questioned its methods and conclusions. Along with the deaths, the report said that the lives of 325 million people, primarily in poor countries, were being seriously affected by climate chan...\n\nQ: What do we learn about the Forum's report from the passage?", "options": ["It was challenged by some climate and risk experts.", "It aroused a lot of interest in the scientific circles.", "It was warmly received by environmentalists.", "It caused a big stir in developing countries."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 686, "question": "Dear John, My name is Amber and I want to share my story with you because what you've shared about life and positive energy has changed my life. This past year has been one of the hardest for me. I felt I was stuck in a position that had nothing to do with what I wanted to do with my life. In January, after two years of being together, my boyfriend left me. I read your blog every morning as I drink my coffee at work, but it wasn't until this March that I told myself \"no more negativity\" as you taught readers in your blog. Since then I've got into new habits at work to keep my energy positive. When people walk in the front door, I'm the first face they see, so I smile big when I say \"good morning\" to them, especially on Mondays. Instead of waiting for someone to ask me for help, I offer it ...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that Amber  _", "options": ["didn't like her boyfriend", "spent a lot of time online", "wasn't satisfied with her job", "received very good education"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2293, "question": "Recreational tree climbing is taking root in the ecotourism industry, and it's sending guys like Tim Kovar to far off reaches of the globe. Kovar, a tree-climbing instructor, recently returned to the U.S. from Brazil, where he spent time developing a tree-climbing operation thanks to the \"slow travel\" movement. Slow travel, is like the slow food movement, the practice of giving fast food in favor of homegrown cooking--the kind that takes hours to prepare and enjoy. Likewise, slow travel urges visitors to experience a place's natural surroundings and learn about the ecology in a way not afforded by extreme games. \"Tree climbing is a slow activity,\" says Kovar. \"It's not something you do quickly and then you're on to the next thing or event.\" There is no such thing as a quick climb, especial...\n\nQ: Sophia Sparks prefers the term \"inspirational tree climbing\" because it   _  .", "options": ["provide people with more chances to play outside", "bring a lot of pleasure to life", "Deepens personal love between each other", "Makes people realize they should protect trees"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2635, "question": "I took the bus to work for many years. No one knew each other; the passengers all sat there sleepily in the morning. The bus was cheerless and silent. One of the passengers was a small gray-haired man who took the bus to the center for senior citizens every morning. No one ever paid very much attention to him. One July morning he said good morning to the driver and smiled. The driver nodded guardedly . The rest of us were silent. The next day, the old man boarded with a big smile and said in a loud voice: \"A very good morning to you all!\" Some of us looked up, amazed, and murmured \"Good Morning\" in reply. The following weeks, our friend was dressed in a nice old suit and tie. His thin hair had been carefully combed. He said good morning to us every day and we gradually began to nod and tal...\n\nQ: What are we sure about the old man?", "options": ["His name was Charlie.", "He worked at the center for senior citizens.", "He got sick over the weekend.", "He was in great sorrow when we saw him the next Monday."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 935, "question": "When she looked ahead, Florence Chadwick saw nothing but a solid wall of fog. Her body was numb .She had been swimming for nearly sixteen hours. Already she was the first woman to swim the English Channel in both directions. Now, at age 34,her goal was to become the first woman to swim from Catalina Island to the California coast. On that fourth of July morning in 1952,the sea was like an ice bath and the fog was so thick that she could hardly see her support boats. Sharks swam toward her lone figure, only to be driven away by rifle shots. Against the frigid grip of the sea, she struggled on--hour after hour--while millions watched on national television. Alongside Florence in one of the boats , her mother and her trainer offered encouragement. They told her it wasn't much farther. But all...\n\nQ: Why didn't Florence swim across the Catalina Channel for the first time?", "options": ["Because she was too tired to go on swimming.", "Because the fog was so thick that she couldn't see her support boats clearly.", "Because she couldn't see the goal on land.", "Because the sea water was too cold."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2734, "question": "The intelligence times provide us much convenience,but at the same time,some of our abilities are being weakened gradually. 1. Memorizing phone numbers It was annoying to remember numbers. Now we simply add them to our contacts list. That usually works well unless our device is lost,stolen,or damaged. No one can be expected to remember all their contact numbers. What we can do is memorize 5 of our most important contact numbers. This should include a mixture of family,friends and business. If you're really ambitious you can memorize 5 contacts for each category. 2. Map-reading skills The convenience and effectiveness of GPS guidance systems and digital maps generated by search engines is unquestionable. They've definitely made our lives easier. What we don't get from using these devices an...\n\nQ: The author of the text seems to   _  .", "options": ["be worried that we might lose some basic abilities in intelligence society", "point out to us the abilities one should have for adapting to the modem society", "be glad that people will regain these abilities by using them often in daily life", "find out that these abilities will probably make modern people different from before"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 436, "question": "Teenage life is quite dramatic but that doesn't mean you cannot enjoy your life in these years. Even with your daily troubles, your life is not very hard if you know how to deal with them. I know exactly how you feel. Life as a teenager can be hard. You are not a kid anymore, because you are smart enough to observe and analyze your surroundings. However, you are still not an adult because there are still lots of experiences that you need to have and lessons that you need to learn from these experiences. To top it all, the hormonal imbalance in your body can really mess you up emotionally. I have been there. I was in it for 6 years exploring what life is about. As a teenager, I had a major problem with completing my chores on time. And at that time, all that I need to do was finish my assig...\n\nQ: Whom is the text intended for?", "options": ["Parents", "Teachers", "Teenagers", "Scientists"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 51, "question": "\"What is the most important thing you've done in your life?\" The question was put to me during a presentation I gave to a group of lawyers. The answer came to me in an instant. It's not the one I gave, because the situation was not right. As a lawyer in the entertainment industry, I knew the audience wanted to hear some amusing stories about my work with well-known people, but here's the true answer: The most important thing I've ever done occurred on October 8,1990. I began the day playing tennis with an old friend I hadn't seen for a while. Between points we talked about what had been happening in each other's lives. He and his wife had just had a baby boy, who was keeping them up at night. While we were playing, a car came screaming up the road toward the courts. It was my friend's fath...\n\nQ: When he saw his friend rush to the hospital, the author could not decide whether to follow mainly because he thought    _   .", "options": ["he had to stay with his family", "his friend did not need his help.", "he would not be of much help", "the baby would be in the doctor's care"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2064, "question": "With more and more wineries offering organic varieties to lower their eco-footprint , it's no surprise that they're looking at the environmental impacts of their packaging as well. The making of conventional glass bottles and the corks uses large quantities of natural resources and causes a lot of pollution. Beyond manufacturing, the transport of wine in glass bottles across the country and around the world also has its environmental effect. Trucking all the heavy glass bottles causes a much larger carbon footprint than the transportation of much lighter boxed wine. Almost half the weight of an ordinary case of wine comes from the bottles; about 95 percent of the weight of a case of boxed wine is the wine itself. \"A standard wine bottle holds 750 milliliters of wine and causes about 5.2 po...\n\nQ: Compared with glass bottled wine, boxed wine   _  .", "options": ["wastes more natural resources", "is difficult to transport", "causes less eco-footprint", "takes up more space"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 263, "question": "Is It OK to Snap Your Food? Have you ever taken a snap of a luxurious cake or photographed a juicy steak when you eat in restaurants? You may want to share what you eat with your friends or just post part of your daily life onto the Internet. However, such action may be very annoying to other diners, or even to chefs and restaurant owners. Currently, more and more people begin to consider \" foodstagramming\" as very silly and a bad manner. In many restaurants, diners complain of being blinded by flasher , snapped without their permission and disturbed by people climbing on to chairs for a better angle. Even chefs and restaurant owners are annoyed at food photography. A Michelin-starred chef said, \"It's hard to build a memorable evening when flashes are flying every six minutes.\" At the star...\n\nQ: What is foodstagramming?", "options": ["It's a popular practice where diners take photos of their meals and share them online.", "It's a popular practice where dinners take photos of their meals and sells to others.", "It's a habit that people take photos when they eat.", "It's an idea how to take photos of their meals."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1274, "question": "London is the capital of the United Kingdom and the largest city in the European Union. It is the world's largest finacial center and one of the most important cultural centers and its influence on politics, education, entertainment, media, fashion, and the arts contributes to its status as a major global city. Central London is the headquarters of more than half of the UK's top 100 listed companies(the FTSE 100 ) and more than 100 of Europe's 500 largest companies. The city is a major tourist destination for both domestic and overseas visitors. London hosted the 1908 and 1948 Summer Olympic Games and will host the 2012 Summer Olympic Games. London contains four World Heritage Sites: the Tower of London, the historic settlement of Greenwich ;the Royal Botanic Garden, Kew; and the site comp...\n\nQ: Which statement is True ?", "options": ["Central London has 50 of the UK's top 100 listed companies.", "By the year of 2015, London will host the Summer Olympic Games.", "Three are 300 languages spoken within the city.", "The metropolitan area of Paris is the largest one in the EU."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2300, "question": "Law School Essays that Made a Difference Price: US $ 13.95 Paperback 256 pages The Princeton Review ISBN: 0375763457 Face it, and a lot of students have great LSAT scores. The best way for you to stand out in a crowd of applicants to top law schools is to write an exceptional(,) personal statement. This book puts you in the admissions office's seat. It gives you the intimate detailstest scores, GPAs (grade point average), demographic information, and personal statementsof 34 law school hopefuls, then shows you why they got into the colleges they applied to, and why some didn't. It's invaluable information that will help students evaluate their own chances of admission to the most selective law schools in the United States. Business School Essays that Made a Difference Price: US $ 13.95 Pap...\n\nQ: What's the purpose of writing the three texts?", "options": ["To sell the books.", "To make the books easier to read.", "To show the importance of the schools.", "To introduce new authors"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 699, "question": "After their 20-year-old son hanged himself during his winter break from the University of Arizona five years ago, Donna and Phil Satow wondered what signs they have overlooked, and started asking other students for answers. What grew from this soul searching was Ulifeline (www. Ulifeline. org), a Web site where students can get answers to questions about depression by logging on through their universities. The site has been adopted as a resource by over 120 colleges, which can customize it with local information, and over 1.3 million students have logged on with their college ID's. \"It is a very solid Web site that raises awareness of suicide, de-stigmatizes mental illness and encourages people to seek the help they need,\"said Paul Grayson, the director of counseling services at New York U...\n\nQ: Go Ask Alice as mentioned in the passage is  _", "options": ["a side effect caused by some prescription drugs", "intended to counsel college students in mental problems", "a collection of medical responses from students the world over", "meant to describe the various signs of mental disorders"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1708, "question": "Everyone, please think of your biggest personal goal. For real - you can take a second. You've got to feel this to learn it. Take a few seconds and think of your personal biggest goal, okay? Imagine deciding right now that you're going to do it. Imagine telling someone that you meet today what you're going to do. Imagine their congratulations and their high image of you. Doesn't it feel good to say it out loud? Don't you feel one step closer already, like it's already becoming part of your identity? Well, bad news: you should have kept your mouth shut, because that good feeling now will make you less likely to do it. Repeated psychology tests have proved that telling someone your goal makes it less likely to happen. Any time you have a goal, there are some steps that need to be done, some ...\n\nQ: According to the article, when you tell your friends your goals,   _  .", "options": ["you feel more pressure to try to make them happen", "they feel jealous of your satisfaction and stand in your way", "you make yourself believe that you are close to achieving them", "it becomes easier for you to make them come true thanks to the support of others"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 90, "question": "If there is a building which symbolizes a country--such as the Eiffel Tower for France and Sydney Opera House for Australia--then it has to be the Taj Mahal for India. It was set up by Emperor Shah Jahan in 1653 in memory of his wife, Mumtaz Mahal. From the time they got married, they wouldn't be separated. She followed him to wars, advised him on affairs of state, and was loved by his people for her good work. But she died in 1631 during childbirth. The emperor was heart-broken and had the Taj Mahal built as a sign of his love. It took more than 20 years for the Taj Mahal to be built. Workers were brought in, not only from all over India, but from Central Asia too. A total of 20,000 people worked on the building. In 1657, Shah Jahan fell ill, and in 1658 his son Aurangzeb, imprisoned his ...\n\nQ: Which of the following about the Taj Mahal is NOT true?", "options": ["It is a symbol of India.", "It took over 20 years to build the Taj Mahal.", "All workers building the Taj Mahal came from Central Asia.", "The Taj Mahal was built with white marble stones."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1654, "question": "Do you love Beats headphones, True Religion jeans, and UGG shoes? These are some of the most popular brands around. They are also expensive. But some experts say they are not much better than cheaper brands. For example, Jim Wilcox works for Consumer Reports. He tested all kinds of headphones. He says that $80 Koss Pro headphones provide basically the same quality and comfort as Beats. So why do people pay twice or even 10 times as much for the hottest brands? Experts say it's because fashionable, expensive brands send a message. Brands say \"I belong\" or \"I can afford it.\" Some people think that expensive brand names are worth the price. They say that some designer clothes really are top quality and that they last longer than cheaper brands. Some teenagers choose to wear popular brands bec...\n\nQ: What does Edmund think of expensive brands?", "options": ["They are not worth the price.", "They make him feel confident.", "They need to improve their quality.", "They pay too much attention to personal likes."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1045, "question": "Children will find it more difficult to buy cigarettes as vending machines selling tobacco will be officially banned in England today.According to the British Heart Foundation(BHF),around 200,000 young people start smoking regularly in England each year and 11 per cent of l1-to15-year-old regular smokers in England and Wales get their cigarettes from vending machines. Betty McBride, Director of Policy and Communications at the British Heart Foundation,said,\"Thousands of children who are at risk of addiction regularly get tobacco from these machines,which of course,don't ask them to prove their age.With the tobacco industry increasingly depending on young smokers to keep their profits,they're fighting tooth and nail to stop any changes that might hit their bottom line.\" The ban, which makes...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the text that  _", "options": ["plain packaging is a must for cigarettes", "the number of tobacco companies will be limited", "tobacco's harm to health will be put down on packages", "opinions will be asked for on plans of tobacco controlling"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1522, "question": "Dear Ana, In your last letter, you told me that your boss Stephanie was probably looking for a new job and you didn't know how to tell her that you wanted to take her position if she left. Well, I'd like to tell you that there is no polite way to talk about this situation with your boss. After all, you are not one-hundred-percent sure that she is actually job-hunting. Even if you know for sure that she is, you can't, because it's not your business. Still, there are a couple of things that you can do to put yourself in a good position in case your boss does _ in the near future. First, you can have a general conversation with her about your career plans. Say something like, \"You've always been supportive of me, Stephanie, and I'd love you to give me some advice on my professional developmen...\n\nQ: We can learn from Liz's reply that  _  .", "options": ["Ana has never talked about her career plans before", "Ana is very sad to see her boss go as she has helped her a lot", "Ana's boss Stephanie may not be looking for a new job", "there are some training courses in Ana's company now"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2752, "question": "Science Daily (Apr. 27, 2008)-- Dutch ecologist Roxina Soler and her colleagues have discovered that subterranean and aboveground herbivorous insects can communicate with each other by using plants as telephones. Subterranean insects issue chemical warning signals through the leaves of the plant. This way, aboveground insects are warned that the plant is already \"occupied\". Aboveground, leaf-eating insects prefer plants that have not yet been occupied by subterranean root-eating insects. Subterranean insects send out chemical signals through the leaves of the plant, which warn the aboveground insects about their presence. This messaging makes it possible for spatially-separated insects to avoid each other, so that they do not compete for, the same plant. In recent years it has been discove...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Communication between different insects", "How do animals avoid competition?", "Insects use plants as telephones", "When plants have subterranean residents"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1570, "question": "Most people know that awkward feeling when you step into an elevator with other people and try not to make eye contact. But new research suggests it may be down to a subconscious power struggle being played out as you make your way up or down. A study found that people decide where they stand based on a micro social grading, established within seconds of entering the lift. Rebekah Rousi, a Ph.D. student in cognitive science, conducted an study of elevator behaviour in two of the tallest office buildings in Adelaide, Australia. As part of her research, she took a total of 30 lift rides in the two buildings, and discovered there was an established order to where people tended stand. In a blog, she writes that more senior men seemed to direct themselves towards the back of the elevator cabins...\n\nQ: Why do women choose to stand in the front?", "options": ["Because they are too shy to make eye contact with others.", "Because they can have a view of everyone else.", "Because they want to show their power.", "Because they want to watch the monitors."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3039, "question": "Once upon a time a peacock and a tortoise became great friends. The peacock lived in a tree on the bank of the stream in which the tortoise had his home, and every day the peacock danced near the stream and displayed his gay plumage for the amusement of his friend. Unfortunately, one day a bird-catcher caught the peacock and was about to take him away to the market. The unhappy bird begged his captor to allow him to say goodbyeto his friend -- the tortoise. The bird-catcher agreed and took the peacock to the tortoise, who was greatly astonished when he saw his friend become a captive. The tortoise asked the bird-catcher to let the peacock go, but the bird-catcher laughed at his request, saying that was his livelihood. The tortoise then said, \"If I give you a handsome present, will you let ...\n\nQ: In this passage, the author is telling us that   _  .", "options": ["human beings shouldn't trust a tortoise", "if we are too greedy, we may get nothing", "human beings shouldn't catch animals", "the bird-catcher shouldn't have asked for another pearl"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2514, "question": "The interview had been going on for about 20 minutes and everything seems to be going well. Then,suddenly,the interviewer asks an unexpected question,\"Which is more important,law or Dove?\" Job applicants in the West increasingly find themselves asked strange questions like this. And the signs are that this is beginning to happen in China. Employers want people skilled,enthusiastic and devoted. So these are the qualities that any reasonably intelligent job applicants will try to show no matter what his or her actual feelings are. In response,employers are increasingly using questions which try and show the applicant's true personality. The question in the first paragraph comes from a test called the Keirsey Personality Sorter. It is an attempt to discover how people solve problems,rather th...\n\nQ: Why do the interviewers ask such questions?", "options": ["They want to discover what the interviewees know.", "They are curious about the answers.", "They try to discover the ability of the interviewees solving problems.", "They just ask questions without thinking much."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1314, "question": "The Isle of Wight, off the south coast of England, is the best place in Europe for discovering dinosaur bones. Dinosaur Farm Museum was established in 1993. Since then, the museum has introduced the study of old bones to many more people. What we offer Visitors can enjoy our displays, or watch us cleaning dinosaur bones and other fossils found on the island's beaches. The museum has a variety of different fossils, many of them never displayed to the public before. As more are discovered all the time, you can be sure of seeing something new each time you visit. We have a free Fossil Identification Service, so you can bring in any fossils you have and find out what they are. In addition, we have a reasonably-priced Museum Shop, where you can buy a souvenir of your visit. You could also bring...\n\nQ: Why are there always new fossils to see at the museum?", "options": ["New fossils are discovered constantly.", "People keep donating fossils to the museum.", "Only a few of the fossils are displayed each day.", "The museum exchanges fossils with other museums."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3194, "question": "A long road leads through the woods to Don Robinson's unfinished house. Wearing dirty sneakers and a shirt with holes, Don Robinson is an 81-year-old Missouri businessman. Although he's rich, he didn't use his money to buy himself a grand home. Instead, he used it to buy wild land. Robinson has decided to donate 843 acres of his own personal _ to the Department of Natural Resources after his death, which can then be used to create a new state park. His generous donation is the same size as New York City's Central Park. It is said that it's the largest land donation to happen in the last 25 years. How did he come up with this idea? For Robinson, the idea of donation came from his respect for the land and the environment. He doesn't have children to pass it onto. He hoped that someone would ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements about is TRUE?", "options": ["Don Robinson paid much attention to how much his donation was worth.", "New York City's Central Park was built with Don Robinson's help.", "Don Robinson had many children and lived with them.", "The idea of donation came from Robinson's respect for the land and the environment."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 819, "question": "Long after the 1998 World Cup was won, disappointed fans were still cursing the disputed refereeing decisions that denied victory to their team. A researcher was appointed to study the performance of some top referees. The researcher organized an experimental tournament involving four youth teams. Each match lasted an hour, divided into three periods of 20 minutes during which different referees were in charge. Observers noted down the referees' errors, of which there were 61 over the tournament. Converted to a standard match of 90 minutes, each referee made almost 23 mistakes, a remarkably high number. The researcher then studied the videotapes to analyse the matches in detail. Surprisingly, he found that errors were more likely when the referees were close to the incident. When the offic...\n\nQ: The number of refereeing errors in the experimental matches was   _  .", "options": ["slightly above average", "higher than in the 1998 World Cup", "quite unexpected", "as high as in a standard match"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1728, "question": "When we see well, we do not think about our eyes very often. It is only when we cannot see perfectly that we realize how important our eyes are. People who are near-sighted can only see things that are very close to their eyes. Everything else seems blurry (unclear). Many people who do a lot of work, such as writing, reading and sewing become near--sighted. People who are far-sighted _ from just the opposite problem. They can see things that are far away, but they have difficulty in reading a book unless they hold it at arm's length. If they want to do much reading, they must get glasses, too. Other people do not see clearly because their eyes are not exactly the right shape. They have what is called astigmatism . This, too, can be corrected by glasses. Some people's eyes become cloudy bec...\n\nQ: Having two eyes instead of one is particularly useful for  _  .", "options": ["seeing at night", "seeing objects far away", "looking over a wide area", "judging distances"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2325, "question": "Starting college can be a difficult experience. You have to deal with new responsibilities, growing independence, a challenging course load, and of course, the social scene. When a roommate is thrown into the mix, it may feel like you're struggling with all that stuff while living in a small box with a stranger. But having a roommate doesn't need to be one more thing to worry about. When students go into their living situations with realistic expectations and a willingness to _ , things can work out just fine. When you first meet your roommate, chances are that you'll be on your best behavior. You want to get along since this is the person who's going to be sharing your living space for the next year. But try to think ahead to potential worst cases, too. For example, imagine it's 2 am and ...\n\nQ: You should try to be polite to your roommate because   _  .", "options": ["you will stay in touch with each other for a year", "you would like to get along well with each other", "something bad must take place in the future", "a stranger is very difficult to deal with actually"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3357, "question": "Iceland, an island just south of the Arctic Circle, has fairly mild winters, thanks to warm ocean currents. Time your vacation here during the winter months to take advantage of off-season deals. Off-season means good deals on flights, hotels and tours. You may also find that the locals are a bit friendlier and more welcoming when tourists aren't arriving in crowds. In the winter months, there are less than seven hours of daylight; thus, chances are good you'll catch sight of the northern lights. Sunsets are also beautiful at this time, making for some great photo opportunities. In Iceland, winter is the perfect time to hike glaciers, go ice climbing, explore caves made out of hardened lava and much more. One of the most popular activities is off-roading in a specially-equipped \"super jeep...\n\nQ: What does this article explain?.", "options": ["Some of Iceland's urban cultural attractions.", "A way t reduce the cost of a trip to Iceland.", "Reasons for visiting Iceland in June and July.", "The average price for a short tour of Iceland."], "answer": 1}]